# **INFO**

Full Name: Juan Carlos Moreno Munevar

Phone: 517 2440

Phone Mobile: 321 343 9369 e-mail: jcmm.info@gmail.com

\_\_\_\_\_

# **SUMMARY**

Creative Front-End Developer passionate about web development scripting languages (HTML, CSS and Javascript), with outstanding experience developing standards-compliant & browsers compatible websites and applications in deadline-oriented environments. With 9 + years of experience related to development of solutions and web graphics, High Skills for organization and planning of interactive projects. Like a Professional Graphic Designer, I have the capability to integrate the usability and design giving a holistic approach to my work.

\_\_\_\_\_

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

OSG June 2011 – Currently

## **Interactive Web Developer**

Web Sites Development with the following specialties:

- Development experience with scripting languages: HTML, CSS and Javascript.
- Experience building responsive websites.
- knowledge in: html5 (jadejs), css3, javascript (Es6, angular, jquery, three.js).
- Automation: grunt, gulp.
- CSS processors (Less, SASS).
- Cross-browser compatibility.

Freelance August 2011 – June 2013

#### **FrontEnd**

Sites Development with the following specialties:

- Development experience with scripting languages: HTML, CSS and Javascript.
- Experience building responsive websites.
- CSS processors (Less, SASS).
- Cross-browser compatibility.

## Mccann March 2010 – june 2011

## **Interactive Web Designer / Interactive Web Developer**

Designer and Web Sites Development with the following specialties:

- Strong knowledge of creating and designing an interactive experience across multiple digital platforms.
- Development experience with scripting languages: HTML, CSS and Javascript.
- Strong working experience with Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects and image optimization for web.

Digiway January 2008 – february 2010

### **Designer and Web Sites Development with the following specialties**

- Strong knowledge of creating and designing an interactive experience across multiple digital platforms.
- Experience with development with scripting languages: HTML, CSS and action script 3.
- Strong working experience with Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects and image optimization for web.

\_\_\_\_\_

# **EDUCATION**

Jorge Tadeo Lozano University - Graphic Designer, Bogota — Colombia 1999 - 2005 Web Sites Development (Informal course) - Jorge Tadeo Lozano

\_\_\_\_\_